Finding Aid for the James G. Stahlman Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Community Activities
  - Metropolitan School System, Juvenile Court Records (Box IX-4, Folder 14)
  - Middle Tennessee Council, Boy Scouts of America, Outgoing Correspondence, 1934 - 1973 (Box IX-4, Folder 15)
  - Middle Tennessee Council, Boy Scouts of America, Outgoing Correspondence, 1974 - 1976 (Box IX-4, Folder 16)
  - Middle Tennessee Council, Boy Scouts of America, Incoming Correspondence, Akers - Benedict (Box IX-4, Folder 17)
  - Middle Tennessee Council, Boy Scouts of America, Incoming Correspondence, Boxwell - Craig (Box IX-4, Folder 18)
  - Middle Tennessee Council, Boy Scouts of America, Incoming Correspondence, Dyer - Liff (Box IX-4, Folder 19)
  - Middle Tennessee Council, Boy Scouts of America, Incoming Correspondence, Reneker - Weaver, unidentified (Box IX-4, Folder 20)
  - Middle Tennessee Council, Boy Scouts of America, Clippings, “Akers ...” - “Is.. .” (Box IX-4, Folder 21)
  - Middle Tennessee Council, Boy Scouts of America, Clippings, “Left ...” - “United.. .” (Box IX-4, Folder 22)
  - Middle Tennessee Council, Boy Scouts of America, Annual Reports, 1973 - 1975 (Box IX-5, Folder 1)
  - Middle Tennessee Council, Boy Scouts of America, Events, 1966 - 1974 (Box IX-5, Folder 2)
  - Middle Tennessee Council, Boy Scouts of America, 1972 - 1975 (Box IX-5, Folder 3)
  - Middle Tennessee Council, Boy Scouts of America, Jet Potter Center (Box IX-5, Folder 4)
  - Middle Tennessee Council, Boy Scouts of America, Officers & Board, 1974 - 1976 (Box IX-5, Folder 5)
  - Middle Tennessee Council, Boy Scouts of America, Press Release (Box IX-5, Folder 6)
  - Middle Tennessee Council, Boy Scouts of America, Smoke Signals Newsletter, 1975 - 1976 (Box IX-5, Folder 7)
  - Middle Tennessee Heart Association, 1973 - 1975 (Box IX-5, Folder 8)
  - Nashville Baseball Club (Box IX-5, Folder 9)
  - Nashville Board of Park Commissioners, Outgoing Correspondence (Box IX-5, Folder 10)
  - Nashville Board of Park Commissioners, Outgoing (Box IX-5, Folder 11)
  - Nashville Board of Park Commissioners, Outgoing, 1941 - 1945 (Box IX-5, Folder 12)
  - Nashville Board of Park Commissioners, Outgoing (Box IX-5, Folder 13)
  - Nashville Board of Park Commissioners, Outgoing, Jan. - Jun. 1947 (Box IX-5, Folder 14)
  - Nashville Board of Park Commissioners, Outgoing, Jul. 1947 - Apr. 1948 (Box IX-5, Folder 15)
  - Nashville Board of Park Commissioners, Outgoing, May - Nov. 2, 1948 (Box IX-5, Folder 16)
  - Nashville Board of Park Commissioners, Outgoing, Nov. 9, 1948 - Jan. 1949 (Box IX-5, Folder 17)
  - Nashville Board of Park Commissioners, Outgoing, Feb. - May 2, 1949 (Box IX-5, Folder 18)
  - Nashville Board of Park Commissioners, Outgoing, May 16 - Dec. 1949 (Box IX-5, Folder 19)
  - Nashville Board of Park Commissioners, Outgoing, Jan. - Mar. 1950 (Box IX-5, Folder 20)
  - Nashville Board of Park Commissioners, Outgoing, Apr. - May, 1950 (Box IX-5, Folder 21)
  - Nashville Board of Park Commissioners, Outgoing, Jun. - Oct. 1950, undated (Box IX-5, Folder 22)
  - Nashville Board of Park Commissioners, Incoming Correspondence, Aiken - Buntin (Box IX-6, Folder 1)
  - Nashville Board of Park Commissioners, Incoming, Cadved - Coolidge (Box IX-6, Folder 2)
  - Nashville Board of Park Commissioners, Incoming, Costello - Craig (Box IX-6, Folder 3)
  - Nashville Board of Park Commissioners, Incoming, Currey (Box IX-6, Folder 4)
  - Nashville Board of Park Commissioners, Incoming, Davis - Duncan (Box IX-6, Folder 5)
  - Nashville Board of Park Commissioners, Incoming, Edens - Fergerson (Box IX-6, Folder 6)
  - Nashville Board of Park Commissioners, Incoming, Fort - Gilbert (Box IX-6, Folder 7)
  - Nashville Board of Park Commissioners, Incoming, Glenn - Jones (Box IX-6, Folder 8)
  - Nashville Board of Park Commissioners, Incoming, Keeble - Loventhal (Box IX-6, Folder 9)
  - Nashville Board of Park Commissioners, Incoming, McAnn - Murray (Box IX-6, Folder 10)
  - Nashville Board of Park Commissioners, Incoming, Nashville ... - Sharp (Box IX-6, Folder 11)
  - Nashville Board of Park Commissioners, Incoming, Skinner (Box IX-6, Folder 12)
  - Nashville Board of Park Commissioners, Incoming, Skinner (Box IX-6, Folder 13)
  - Nashville Board of Park Commissioners, Incoming, Skinner (Box IX-6, Folder 14)
  - Nashville Board of Park Commissioners, Incoming, Skinner (Box IX-6, Folder 15)
  - Nashville Board of Park Commissioners, Incoming, Skinner (Box IX-6, Folder 16)
  - Nashville Board of Park Commissioners, Incoming, Skinner (Box IX-6, Folder 17)
  - Nashville Board of Park Commissioners, Incoming, Skinner (Box IX-6, Folder 18)
  - Nashville Board of Park Commissioners, Incoming, Skinner (Box IX-7, Folder 1)
  - Nashville Board ofPark Commissioners, Incoming, Skinner (Box IX-7, Folder 2)
  - Nashville Board of Park Commissioners, Incoming, Skinner (Box IX-7, Folder 3)
  - Nashville Board ofPark Commissioners, Incoming, Skinner (Box IX-7, Folder 4)
  - Nashville Board ofPark Commissioners, Incoming, Spaulding- Tupper (Box IX-7, Folder 5)
  - Nashville Board ofPark Commissioners, Incoming, Wagner- West (Box IX-7, Folder 6)
  - Nashville Board of Park Commissioners, Incoming, West Nashville- Wroton (Box IX-7, Folder 7)
  - Nashville Board ofPark Commissioners, Incoming, Yokley- Young, unidentified (Box IX-7, Folder 8)
  - Nashville Board of Park Commissioners, Clippings (Box IX-7, Folder 9)
  - Nashville Board of Park Commissioners, Clippings (Box IX-7, Folder 10)
  - Nashville Board ofPark Commissioners, Clippings (Box IX-7, Folder 11)
  - Nashville Board ofPark Commissioners, Clippings (Box IX-7, Folder 12)
  - Nashville Board ofPark Commissioners, Act Creating the Park Commission (Box IX-7, Folder 13)
  - Nashville Board ofPark Commissioners, Annual Report (Box IX-7, Folder 14)
  - Nashville Board ofPark Commissioners, Commisioners (Box IX-7, Folder 15)
  - Nashville Board ofPark Commissioners, Departmental Assignments (Box IX-7, Folder 16)
  - Nashville Board ofPark Commissioners, Eulogy for William Hume (Box IX-7, Folder 17)
  - Nashville Board ofPark Commissioners, Events, 1940 - 1949 (Box IX-7, Folder 18)
  - Nashville Board ofPark Commissioners, Fauna (Box IX-7, Folder 19)
  - Nashville Board of Park Commissioners, Financial (Box IX-8, Folder 1)
  - Nashville Board of Park Commissioners, Financial (Box IX-8, Folder 2)
  - Nashville Board of Park Commissioners, Financial, Jan. - Sep. 1940 (Box IX-8, Folder 3)
  - Nashville Board of Park Commissioners, Financial, Oct. - Dec. 1940, and the Annual Report (Box IX-8, Folder 4)
  - Nashville Board of Park Commissioners, Financial (Box IX-8, Folder 5)
  - Nashville Board of Park Commissioners, Financial (Box IX-8, Folder 6)
  - Nashville Board of Park Commissioners, Financial (Box IX-8, Folder 7)
  - Nashville Board of Park Commissioners, Financial, 1944 - 1945 (Box IX-9, Folder 1)
  - Nashville Board of Park Commissioners, Financial, Jan. - Jul. 1946 (Box IX-9, Folder 2)
  - Nashville Board of Park Commissioners, Financial, Aug. - Dec. 1946 (Box IX-9, Folder 3)
  - Nashville Board of Park Commissioners, Financial, Jan. - July 1947 (Box IX-9, Folder 4)
  - Nashville Board of Park Commissioners, Financial, Aug. - Dec. 1947 (Box IX-9, Folder 5)
  - Nashville Board of Park Commissioners, Financial, Jan. -Aug. 1948 (Box IX-9, Folder 6)
  - Nashville Board of Park Commissioners, Financial, Sep. - Dec. 1948 (Box IX-9, Folder 7)
  - Nashville Board of Park Commissioners, Financial, Jan. - Jun. 1949 (Box IX-10, Folder 1)
  - Nashville Board of Park Commissioners, Financial, Jul. Dec. 1949, 1950 (Box IX-10, Folder 2)
  - Nashville Board of Park Commissioners, Fragments (Box IX-10, Folder 3)
  - Nashville Board of Park Commissioners, Golf Programs (Box IX-10, Folder 4)
  - Nashville Board of Park Commissioners, McCabe Field (Box IX-10, Folder 5)
  - Nashville Board of Park Commissioners, Maryland Hunt Club (Box IX-10, Folder 6)
  - Nashville Board of Park Commissioners, Minutes, 1939 (Box IX-10, Folder 7)
  - Nashville Board of Park Commissioners, Minutes, 1940 - 1942 (Box IX-10, Folder 8)
  - Nashville Board of Park Commissioners, Minutes, 1943 - 1946 (Box IX-10, Folder 9)
  - Nashville Board of Park Commissioners, Minutes (Box IX-10, Folder 10)
  - Nashville Board of Park Commissioners, Minutes (Box IX-11, Folder 1)
  - Nashville Board of Park Commissioners, Minutes (Box IX-11, Folder 2)
  - Nashville Board of Park Commissioners, Minutes (Box IX-11, Folder 3)
  - Nashville Board of Park Commissioners, Notes, undated (Box IX-11, Folder 4)
  - Nashville Board of Park Commissioners, Parthenon (Box IX-11, Folder 5)
  - Nashville Board of Park Commissioners, Percy Warner Park (Box IX-11, Folder 6)
  - Nashville Board of Park Commissioners, Playground (Box IX-11, Folder 7)
  - Nashville Board of Park Commissioners, Report of Grounds & Building Committee (Box IX-11, Folder 8)
  - Nashville Board of Park Commissioners, Resolution Honoring Jgs, 1950 (Box IX-11, Folder 9)
  - Nashville Board of Park Commissioners, Swimming Pools (Box IX-11, Folder 10)
  - Nashville Boys Club (Box IX-11, Folder 11)
  - Nashville Children’s Theatre (Box IX-11, Folder 12)
  - Nashville Court No. 92, Royal Order of Jesters, Outgoing, 1943 - 1973 (Box IX-11, Folder 13)
  - Nashville Court No. 92, Royal Order of Jesters, Incoming, Burton (Box IX-11, Folder 14)
  - Nashville Court No. 92, Royal Order of Jesters, Incoming, Holder (Box IX-11, Folder 15)
  - Nashville Court No. 92, Royal Order of Jesters, Incoming, Laskey - Watson (Box IX-11, Folder 16)
  - Nashville Court No. 92, Royal Order of Jesters, Incoming, Watson (Box IX-11, Folder 17)
  - Nashville Court No. 92, Royal Order of Jesters, Incoming, Watson (Box IX-11, Folder 18)
  - Nashville Court No. 92, Royal Order of Jesters, Roster & By-Laws (Box IX-11, Folder 19)
  - Nashville History (Box IX-12, Folder 1)
  - Nashville History, Clippings (Box IX-12, Folder 2)
  - Nashville History, Publications (Box IX-12, Folder 3)
  - Nashville Symphony (Box IX-12, Folder 4)
  - National Anti-Syphilis Committee (Box IX-12, Folder 5)
  - Newcomer Society (Box IX-12, Folder 6)
  - Oak Hill, City of (Box IX-12, Folder 7)
  - Oak Hill School (Box IX-12, Folder 8)
  - Office of Civil Defense (Box IX-12, Folder 9)
  - The Old Woman’s Home (Box IX-12, Folder 10)
  - Phoenix Lodge No. 131 (Box IX-12, Folder 11)
  - Public Library of Nashville and Davidson County (Box IX-12, Folder 12)
  - Rannor Lake Sportsmen’s Club (Box IX-12, Folder 13)
  - Rotary Club of Nashville (Box IX-12, Folder 14)
  - Royal Arch Masons (Box IX-12, Folder 15)
  - Ryman Auditorium (Box IX-12, Folder 16)
  - St. George’s Church (Box IX-12, Folder 17)
  - St. Thomas Hospital (Box IX-12, Folder 18)
  - Scottish Rite of Freemasonry, Outgoing, 1931-1974, undated (Box IX-12, Folder 19)
  - Scottish Rite of Freemasonry, Incoming, Benedict - Neely (Box IX-12, Folder 20)
  - Scottish Rite of Freemasonry, Outgoing, Norman - Woodroof (Box IX-12, Folder 21)
  - Scottish Rite of Freemasonry, Clippings (Box IX-12, Folder 22)
  - Scottish Rite of Freemasonry, Events (Box IX-12, Folder 23)
  - Scottish Rite of Freemasonry, Publications (Box IX-13, Folder 1)
  - Scottish Rite of Freemasonry, Photographs (Box IX-13, Folder 2)
  - Sulfur Dell Club (Box IX-13, Folder 3)
  - Tennessee Botanical Gardens (Box IX-13, Folder 4)
  - Tennessee Council on Economic Education (Box IX-13, Folder 5)
  - Tennessee Country Gentlemen (Box IX-13, Folder 6)
  - Tennessee Monument Commission (Box IX-13, Folder 7)
  - Tennessee Performing Arts Center (Box IX-13, Folder 8)
  - Tennessee Society of the Sons of the American Revolution (Box IX-13, Folder 9)
  - Tennessee Society of the Sons of the American Revolution (Box IX-13, Folder 10)
  - Tourist & Convention Bureau (Box IX-13, Folder 11)
  - Town Meeting 1976 (Box IX-13, Folder 12)
  - Trevecca Nazarene College (Box IX-13, Folder 13)
  - United Way (Box IX-13, Folder 14)
  - Veterans of Foreign Wars (Box IX-13, Folder 15)
  - West End Methodist Church (Box IX-13, Folder 16)
  - Westminster Presbyterian Church (Box IX-13, Folder 17)
  - WLAC.TV (Box IX-13, Folder 18)
  - Women’s Field Army (Box IX-13, Folder 19)
  - Young Men’s Christian Association (Box IX-13, Folder 20)
  - Young Women’s Christian Association (Box IX-13, Folder 21)
- Personal Collections
  - Book File, Clippings (Box X-1, Folder 1)
  - Book File, Notes, Outline, Biographical, undated (Box X-1, Folder 2)
  - Book File, Notes, Newspaper Clipping, undated (Box X-1, Folder 3)
  - Book File, Notes, Philosophy of Life, undated (Box X-1, Folder 4)
  - Book File, Notes, Politics, undated (Box X-1, Folder 5)
  - Book File, Notes, Unforgettable, undated (Box X-1, Folder 6)
  - Book File, Notes, Unidentified, undated (Box X-1, Folder 7)
  - Book File, Photos (Box X-1, Folder 8)
  - Clippings (Box X-1, Folder 9)
  - Destin, Florida (Box X-1, Folder 10)
  - Family, Ann Stahlman (Box X-1, Folder 11)
  - Family, E. B. Stahlman, Jr. (Box X-1, Folder 12)
  - Family, Edward C. Stahlman (Box X-1, Folder 13)
  - Family, Effye Stahlman (Box X-1, Folder 14)
  - Family, Frank C. Stahlman (Box X-1, Folder 15)
  - Family, Gladys Stahlman (Box X-1, Folder 16)
  - Family, James G. Stahlman, Atlanta Law School (Box X-1, Folder 17)
  - Family, James G. Stahlman, Biographical (Box X-1, Folder 18)
  - Family, James G. Stahlman (Box X-1, Folder 19)
  - Family, James G. Stahlman, Estate & Body Disposition (Box X-1, Folder 20)
  - Family, James G. Stahlman, Diplomas (Box X-1, Folder 21)
  - Family, James G. Stahlman, Financial (Box X-1, Folder 22)
  - Family, James G. Stahlman, Geneology (Box X-1, Folder 23)
  - Family, James G. Stahlman, Sheriffs Office (Box X-1, Folder 24)
  - Familv. James G. Stahlman. Standard Series of Life and Work of St. Paul (Box X-1, Folder 25)
  - Family, Mary Geddes Stahlman (Box X-1, Folder 26)
  - Family, Mildred Stahlman (Box X-1, Folder 27)
  - Family, Sylvia Stahlman (Box X-1, Folder 28)
  - Family, Stahlman Building (Box X-1, Folder 29)
  - Miscellaneous (Box X-2, Folder 1)
  - Publications (Box X-2, Folder 2)
  - Publications (Box X-2, Folder 3)
  - Publications, 1926 - 1933 (Box X-2, Folder 4)
  - Tennessee Centennial Exposition (Box X-2, Folder 5)
  - Webb School, Outgoing, 1932 - 1936 (Box X-2, Folder 6)
  - Webb School, Outgoing, 1937 - May 3, 1945 (Box X-2, Folder 7)
  - Webb School, Outgoing, Nov. 12, 1945-1946 (Box X-2, Folder 8)
  - Webb School, Outgoing, 1947 - July 5, 1951 (Box X-2, Folder 9)
  - Webb School, Outgoing, Aug. 9, 1951 - 1954 (Box X-2, Folder 10)
  - Webb School, Outgoing, 1964 - 1976 (Box X-2, Folder 11)
  - Webb School, Incoming, Abernathy - Elliott (Box X-2, Folder 12)
  - Webb School, Incoming, Ewing - Follin (Box X-2, Folder 13)
  - Webb School, Incoming, Follin - Guerry (Box X-2, Folder 14)
  - Webb School, Incoming, Hale - Irvin (Box X-2, Folder 15)
  - Webb School, Incoming, Jones, Gary M. (Box X-2, Folder 16)
  - Webb School, Incoming, Jones, Gary M. (Box X-3, Folder 1)
  - Webb School, Incoming, McDonnell - Ragland (Box X-3, Folder 2)
  - Webb School, Incoming, Redmond - Smith, F. (Box X-3, Folder 3)
  - Webb School, Incoming, Smith, H. - Stokes (Box X-3, Folder 4)
  - Webb School, Incoming, Stuckey - Warer (Box X-3, Folder 5)
  - Webb School, Incoming, Webb, S. - Webb, W. R. (Box X-3, Folder 6)
  - Webb School, Incoming, Webb, W. R. - Wise, W. (Box X-3, Folder 7)
  - Webb School, Alumni Association (Box X-3, Folder 8)
  - Webb School, Alumni Bulletin (Box X-3, Folder 9)
  - Webb School, Board of Trustees, 1952-1976, undated (Box X-3, Folder 10)
  - Webb School, Brochures (Box X-3, Folder 11)
  - Webb School, Charter of Incorporation (Box X-3, Folder 12)
  - Webb School, Class of 1975 (Box X-3, Folder 13)
  - Webb School, Clippings (Box X-3, Folder 14)
  - Webb School, Executive Committee, Minutes, 1951 - 1975 (Box X-3, Folder 15)
  - Webb School, Executive Committee, Minutes, 1975-1976, Proposal for Consideration by the Webb School Executive Committee (Box X-3, Folder 16)
  - Webb School, Financial (Box X-4, Folder 1)
  - Webb School, Financial, Jan. - Jul. 1975 (Box X-4, Folder 2)
  - Webb School, Financial, Sep. - Mar. 1976 (Box X-4, Folder 3)
  - Webb School, Hamilton & Platonic Societies (Box X-4, Folder 4)
  - Webb School, Headmaster’s Report (Box X-4, Folder 5)
  - Webb School, Library Operation, 1974 (Box X-4, Folder 6)
  - Webb School, “A Light to Live By”, by Gary M. Jones (Box X-4, Folder 7)
  - Webb School, Long Range Planning (Box X-4, Folder 8)
  - Webb School, Memorabilia (Box X-4, Folder 9)
  - Webb School, Mini-Week (Box X-4, Folder 10)
  - Webb School, Outline Specification for School Building & Blue Prints (Box X-4, Folder 11)
  - Webb School, President’s Report (Box X-4, Folder 12)
  - Webb School, Principal’s Report (Box X-4, Folder 13)
  - Webb School, 75th Anniversary (Box X-5, Folder 1)
  - Webb School, Societas Amicorum (Box X-5, Folder 2)
  - Webb School, Southern Association of Colleges and Schools (Box X-5, Folder 3)
  - Webb School, Webb’s Summer School (Box X-5, Folder 4)
  - Photographs (Box X-5, Folder 5)
  - Photographs, unidentified (Box X-5, Folder 6)
  - Book: Crinnerungen. by Alfred Don Lirpitz (Box X-5, Folder 7)